New York Statewide Senior Action Council Records
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Subject Files, 1974-1979; 1983-1999; nam_apap111-4; 9.58 cubic ft.
  - Health Care and Medicare, 1983-1998; nam_apap111-4.1; 6.79 cubic ft.
    - Medicaid Cuts Action Group, Prospective Member List, Undated; nam_apap111-4.1_174 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Medicaid Cuts, NYS Health Care Campaign, 1994; nam_apap111-4.1_175 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Medicaid Documentation Issues, 1983-1990; nam_apap111-4.1_176 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Medicaid, Entitlements and Advocacy Training, Brookdale Center on Aging, 1989; nam_apap111-4.1_177 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Medicaid, Entitlements and Advocacy Training, Brookdale Center on Aging, 1996; nam_apap111-4.1_178 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Medicaid Fraud, 1989; 1994; nam_apap111-4.1_179 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Medicaid, Hospital Information, 1990; nam_apap111-4.1_180 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Medicaid Information, Miscellaneous, 1989-1990; nam_apap111-4.1_181 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Medicaid Managed Care Alert, 1995; nam_apap111-4.1_182 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Medicaid, Managed Care Newsletters, 1997-1998; nam_apap111-4.1_183 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - "Medicaid Program in NYS: An Advocate's Handbook", 1988; nam_apap111-4.1_184 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Medicaid Reform, 1988-1990; nam_apap111-4.1_185 (Box 5, Folder 15a-b)
    - Medicaid Restructuring, Bill 52, 1995; nam_apap111-4.1_186 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Medicaid Restructuring Proposal, 1987-1988; nam_apap111-4.1_187 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Medicaid Seminar, Koldin & Levine Law Center, 1990; nam_apap111-4.1_188 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Medicaid Takeover Legislation, 1992; nam_apap111-4.1_189 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Medicaid Workgroup, 1992-1993; nam_apap111-4.1_190 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Medicaid Workgroup Meeting, 1991-1992; nam_apap111-4.1_191 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Medical Care Fraud, Bill A.4689, 1993; nam_apap111-4.1_192 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Medical Payment Dispute Resolution Regulation (DRG), 1990; nam_apap111-4.1_193 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Medical Payment Dispute Resolution System, 1990-1991; nam_apap111-4.1_194 (Box 5, Folder 24a-b)
    - Medical Payment Dispute Resolution System, Request for Proposals to Implement, 1990; nam_apap111-4.1_195 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Medicare, Advocacy/Resolution, 1989-1991; nam_apap111-4.1_196 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Medicare and Medicaid, General Information, 1985-1986; nam_apap111-4.1_197 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - "Medicare and Medicaid Guide", 1988; nam_apap111-4.1_198 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - "Medicare and Medicaid Guide", Law and Legislation, 1987; nam_apap111-4.1_199 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - "Medicare and Medicaid Guide", Supplemental Update, 1986; nam_apap111-4.1_200 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - "Medicare and Medicaid Guide", Supplemental Update, 1989; nam_apap111-4.1_201 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Medicare Beneficiaries Defense Fund, 1992-1993; nam_apap111-4.1_202 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Medicare Billing Rates File, 1989; nam_apap111-4.1_203 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Medicare Bulletins, Brookdale Center on Aging, 1991; nam_apap111-4.1_204 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Medicare Catastrophic Protection Act, 1988-1989; nam_apap111-4.1_205 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Medicare Coalition Conference, 1997; nam_apap111-4.1_206 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Medicare Information, 1986-1988; nam_apap111-4.1_207 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Medicare Information, 1988-1990; nam_apap111-4.1_208 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Medicare Information, 1991-1992; nam_apap111-4.1_209 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Medicare Legislation, Balanced Billing, Bill A. 100, 1993; nam_apap111-4.1_210 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Medicare Legislation, Beneficiaries Protection Amendments, H.R. 1707,1995, nam_apap111-4.1_211 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Medicare Legislation, Cap on Physician Fees, Bill 12304, 1992; nam_apap111-4.1_212 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Medicare Legislative Issues, 1992; nam_apap111-4.1_213 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Medicare Marketing Guidelines, 1996; nam_apap111-4.1_214 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Medicare Reform Conference, 1996; nam_apap111-4.1_215 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Medicare Reform Draft Discussion Document, 1995; nam_apap111-4.1_216 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Medicare Workgroup, 1995; nam_apap111-4.1_217 (Box 6, Folder 13a-b)
    - Medigap Policies and Information, 1991; 1995; nam_apap111-4.1_218 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - National Healthcare Campaign, Insurance Coverage Issues, 1989; nam_apap111-4.1_219 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - National Senior Citizen's Law Center, Report on Nursing Home Issues, 1986; nam_apap111-4.1_220 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - New Yorkers For Accessible Health Coverage (NYFAHC), Memos, 1994; nam_apap111-4.1_221 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Nursing Home Community Coalition Meetings, 1989-1991; 1993; nam_apap111-4.1_222 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Nursing Home Immunizations Report, 1994; nam_apap111-4.1_223 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Nursing Home Industry Report, 1994; nam_apap111-4.1_224 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Nursing Home Issues, 1990; nam_apap111-4.1_225 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Nursing Home Residents' Rights, 1983-1985; 1989; nam_apap111-4.1_226 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Nursing Home Residents' Rights and Issues, 1992; nam_apap111-4.1_227 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Nursing Home Whistleblowers, Amici Curiae Filed with U. S. District Court, 1990; nam_apap111-4.1_228 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - NYAHSA (New York Association of Homes & Services for the Aging), "A Proposal to Reform Medicaid Eligibility for Long Term Care", 1992-1993; nam_apap111-4.1_229 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - NYAHSA Report and Information on Long-Term Care Reform, 1993; nam_apap111-4.1_230 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - NYPHRM V (New York Prospective Hospital Reimbursement Methodology), Briefing Papers and Analysis, 1993; nam_apap111-4.1_231 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - NYPHRM V, Recommendations, 1993; nam_apap111-4.1_232 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - NYS Assembly Committee on Long-Term Care Insurance, 1989-1990; nam_apap111-4.1_233 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - NYS Department of Health Codes Committee, 1996; nam_apap111-4.1_234 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - NYS Department of Health Response to Proposed Cemetery Legislation, Bills S.7455, S.7201, and A.10300, 1994; nam_apap111-4.1_235 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - NYS Legislation, Access to Long-Term Care, Bills S.4674/A.7958, 1993-1994; nam_apap111-4.1_236 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - NYS Legislation, Children's Health Insurance Reform Program, Support Material, 1993; nam_apap111-4.1_237 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - NYS Legislation, Criminal Medical Fraud Bill 4689-A, 1993; nam_apap111-4.1_238 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - NYS Legislation, Health Services Review Bill A.11061, 1992; nam_apap111-4.1_239 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - NYS Legislation, Hearing Aid Industry Bill S.5588B, 1994; nam_apap111-4.1_240 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - NYS Legislation, Hospice Bills S.4201, S.4298, and S.3950-A, 1995; nam_apap111-4.1_241 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - NYS Legislation, Hospital Visitation Bill S.5747, Support Memo, 1994; nam_apap111-4.1_242 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - NYS Legislation, Immunization Bills A.10920./S. 7802, 1994; nam_apap111-4.1_243 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - NYS Legislation, Licensing of Dieticians, Bills A.1578 and #3476, 1985-1989; nam_apap111-4.1_244 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - NYS Legislation, Life Care Communities, Bill S.6327, 1994; nam_apap111-4.1_245 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - NYS Legislation, Long-Term Care Bill A.2713, 1995; nam_apap111-4.1_246 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - NYS Legislation, Patient Abuse/Fraud Bills 7452-A and S.5223, 1989-1990; nam_apap111-4.1_247 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - NYS Legislation, Pet Therapy Bill S.4232, 1995; nam_apap111-4.1_248 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - NYS Legislation, Prescription Drug Prices Bill A.9894/S.7380, 1994; nam_apap111-4.1_249 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - NYS Legislation, Surrogate Bill A.7166, 1994; nam_apap111-4.1_250 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - NYS Legislation, Surrogate Bill A.7166 and Governor's Program Bill #69R, 1994; nam_apap111-4.1_251 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - NYS Legislation, Surrogate Bill A.7166, Statements of Support, 1994; nam_apap111-4.1_252 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - NYS Legislative Reports, 1992-1993; nam_apap111-4.1_253 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - NYS Medical Leave Legislation, Coalition Meeting Material, 1991; nam_apap111-4.1_254 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - NYS Rural Health Coalition, Comparative Analysis of NYPHRM Legislation, 1993; nam_apap111-4.1_255 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - NYS Senate Health Committee Managed Care Hearings, 1995; nam_apap111-4.1_256 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - PASCAS (Personal and Supportive Care Assessment System) Guidelines, Undated; nam_apap111-4.1_257 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Patient Advocacy Project Report, 1989; nam_apap111-4.1_258 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Patients' Bill of Rights, 1986; nam_apap111-4.1_259 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Pepper Commission Report on Affordable Health Care, 1990; nam_apap111-4.1_260 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - PPS (Prospective Payment System) and DRG (Diagnosis Related Groups) Information, 1984-1989; nam_apap111-4.1_261 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - PPS and DRG Information, 1989-1990; nam_apap111-4.1_262 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Primary Care Initiative, 1990; nam_apap111-4.1_263 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Primary Care Legislation Issues, 1992; nam_apap111-4.1_264 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - PRO (Peer Review Organization) Appeals Data, 1987; nam_apap111-4.1_265 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - PRO Contract Negotiations, 1989; nam_apap111-4.1_266 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - PRO Guidelines, 1985-1986; nam_apap111-4.1_267 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - PRO Information and Procedures, 1984-1986; nam_apap111-4.1_268 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - PRO Information and Procedures, 1987-1989; nam_apap111-4.1_269 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - PRO Liaison Committee Report, 1989; nam_apap111-4.1_270 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - PRO News, 1987-1988; nam_apap111-4.1_271 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - PRO Report, 1986; nam_apap111-4.1_272 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - PRO Report, 1990; nam_apap111-4.1_273 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Proposal for Geriatric Medical Education, Undated; nam_apap111-4.1_274 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Public Citizen Health Research Correspondence, 1993; nam_apap111-4.1_275 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Right to Die Campaign, 1990; nam_apap111-4.1_276 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - RUGs (Resource Utilization Groups), 1986-1990; nam_apap111-4.1_277 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - RUGs III: Resource Utilization Groups for Nursing Homes, 1994; nam_apap111-4.1_278 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - SENSES (Statewide Emergency Network for Social and Economic Security) Report on Health Care Coverage for the Uninsured, 1991-1993; nam_apap111-4.1_279 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Single-Payer Plan Support Information, 1994; nam_apap111-4.1_280 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - SOFA (State Office For the Aging) Expanded In-Home Services, 1986; nam_apap111-4.1_281 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - State Hospital Association Telephone Contact Guidelines, 1987; nam_apap111-4.1_282 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Telephone Survey on Emergency Room Care, 1988; nam_apap111-4.1_283 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Testimony Before Assembly Committees, 1993; nam_apap111-4.1_284 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Testimony Before Governor's Health Care Advisory Board, 1993; nam_apap111-4.1_285 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Testimony Before State Hospital Review and Planning Council, 1987; nam_apap111-4.1_286 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Testimonies, Hearings on Medicaid and Health Care Reform, 1990-1992; nam_apap111-4.1_287 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Testimonies, Welfare Reform, Before NYS Senate Standing Committee on Social Services, 1995; nam_apap111-4.1_288 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Universal New York Health Care (UNYCARE), 1989-1991; nam_apap111-4.1_289 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Vermont Medicare Legislation, 1987; 1990; nam_apap111-4.1_290 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Senior Advocacy, 1974-1979; 1984-1999; nam_apap111-4.2; 2.39 cubic ft.
    Files include material on a variety of issues important to New York seniors in the areas of law, taxes, independent living and in-home care, elder abuse, the Right to Die Campaign, age discrimination and continuing education. NYSSAC's work with other groups such as the Capital Area Consortium on Aging and Disability, the Citizens' Utility Board and the State Office of the Aging's Hunger Action Network are documented in files on conferences, workshops and meetings. Included are testimonies given on major issues before legislative bodies, a memorial booklet for activist Rose Kryzak containing a tribute from Governor Mario Cuomo, and various correspondence.
    - AARP Statements and Events, 1995; nam_apap111-4.2_1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Ad Hoc Coalition for the Aging, 1994-1995; nam_apap111-4.2_2 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Advocate Groups for Seniors, 1992; nam_apap111-4.2_3 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Age Discrimination, NYS Office for the Aging Report, 1990; nam_apap111-4.2_4 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Area Agencies for Aging, Directories, 1995; nam_apap111-4.2_5 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Assembly Committee on Aging Schedule, 1989; nam_apap111-4.2_6 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Attorney General Pamphlet "Helping Seniors", Undated; nam_apap111-4.2_7 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Bad Debt and Charity Need, Statistics, 1984-1996; nam_apap111-4.2_8 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Balanced Budget Amendments, 1997; nam_apap111-4.2_9 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Bar Association Collaboration on Legislation, 1989; nam_apap111-4.2_10 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Brookdale Center Advocacy Assistance Training, 1979; nam_apap111-4.2_11 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Budget, Impact on Elder Care, NYS, 1993; nam_apap111-4.2_12 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Budget Reductions, NYS, 1991-1992; nam_apap111-4.2_13 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Capital Area Consortium on Aging and Disability, 1993; nam_apap111-4.2_14 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Capital Area Consortium on Aging and Disability, 1994; nam_apap111-4.2_15 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Center for Community Change Policy Alerts, 1996; nam_apap111-4.2_16 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Citizen Advocacy Center, 1994; nam_apap111-4.2_17 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Coalition Building, Workshop, New York Foundation, 1992; nam_apap111-4.2_18 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - College Curricula for Older Adults, by Hope Bagger, 1974; nam_apap111-4.2_19 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Congressional Election Action, 1998; nam_apap111-4.2_20 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Consortium for the Aging, 1992; nam_apap111-4.2_21 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - CSE (Community Services for the Elderly), 1993; nam_apap111-4.2_22 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - CSE Testimony, 1991; nam_apap111-4.2_23 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - CUB (Citizen's Utility Board) Incorporation, 1991; nam_apap111-4.2_24 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Domestic Partnerships Law, 1991; nam_apap111-4.2_25 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Earned Income Tax Credit Information, 1993; nam_apap111-4.2_26 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - EISEP (Expanding In-Home Services for the Elderly Program), 1989; nam_apap111-4.2_27 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Elder Abuse Bills, S.7012 and Departmental Bill # 673, SOFA, 1994; nam_apap111-4.2_28 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Elder Abuse Conference, 1992; nam_apap111-4.2_29 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Elderline, Independent Living, 1974; 1990; nam_apap111-4.2_30 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Executive Budget Welfare Presentation, NYS Departments of Social Services and Labor, 1996-1997; nam_apap111-4.2_31 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Federal Welfare Reform, Newsletters and News Clippings, 1996; nam_apap111-4.2_32 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Federal Welfare Reform, Reports, 1996; nam_apap111-4.2_33 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Federal Welfare Reform, Source Material, 1996; nam_apap111-4.2_34 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Fiscal Policy Institute Fair Taxes Campaign, 1991; nam_apap111-4.2_35 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Governor Carey's Task Force on Social Security, 1981; nam_apap111-4.2_36 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Governor Cuomo's Press Releases, 1991; nam_apap111-4.2_37 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Hart, Gary, Support Information, 1984; nam_apap111-4.2_38 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Hunger Action Network, 1990; nam_apap111-4.2_39 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Income Distribution Statistics, 1988-1990; nam_apap111-4.2_40 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Innovative Resources Group, Non-Profit Marketing, 1994; nam_apap111-4.2_41 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Intergenerational Lobby Day, 1995; nam_apap111-4.2_42 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Jesuit Volunteer Corps, 1986; nam_apap111-4.2_43 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Job Training Partnership Act, 1989; nam_apap111-4.2_44 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Kryzak, Rose, Essays About, 1976-1986; nam_apap111-4.2_45 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Kryzak, Rose, Memorial Tribute, 1999; nam_apap111-4.2_46 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Labor Issues, 1992; nam_apap111-4.2_47 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Legal Services Programs, Undated; nam_apap111-4.2_48 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Limited Liability Legislation, 1993; nam_apap111-4.2_49 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Massachusetts Senior Action Council, 1985; nam_apap111-4.2_50 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Medicaid Service Changes, NYS Budget, 1995; nam_apap111-4.2_51 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Miscellaneous, 1988-1989; nam_apap111-4.2_52 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Non-Profit Resource Center Meeting, 1994; nam_apap111-4.2_53 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - NYS Assembly Energy Committee Proposals, 1994; nam_apap111-4.2_54 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - NYS Government Budget Memo Packet, 1996; nam_apap111-4.2_55 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - NYS Government Fiscal Outlook, 1996-1997; nam_apap111-4.2_56 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - NYS Legislation, Information, 1985-1987; nam_apap111-4.2_57 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - NYS Legislation, Information, 1988; nam_apap111-4.2_58 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - NYS Legislation, Materials, 1991; nam_apap111-4.2_59 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - NYS Legislation, Materials, 1992; nam_apap111-4.2_60 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - NYS Legislation, Materials, 1993; nam_apap111-4.2_61 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - NYS Legislation on Aging, Memos, 1995-1996; nam_apap111-4.2_62 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - NYS Legislation on Aging, Memos, 1997-1998; nam_apap111-4.2_63 (Box 2, Folder 4a-b)
    - NYS Legislation, Real Estate Advisory Committee, 1993-1994; nam_apap111-4.2_64 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - NYS Legislation, Senior Citizens' Pets in Housing, Bill S.819, 1989; nam_apap111-4.2_65 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - NYS Legislation, Weatherization Funds, Bill S.6066, 1992; nam_apap111-4.2_66 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - NYS Legislative Action Letters, 1990; nam_apap111-4.2_67 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - NYS Legislative Newsletter on the Elderly, 1991; nam_apap111-4.2_68 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - NYS Office for the Aging Advisory Committee, 1996; nam_apap111-4.2_69 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - NYS Office for the Aging, (SOFA) Legislative Memos, 1987; nam_apap111-4.2_70 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - NYS Office for the Aging, Legislative Memos, 1990; nam_apap111-4.2_71 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - NYS Office for the Aging, Legislative Memos, 1992; nam_apap111-4.2_72 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - NYS Senate Legislative Bills on Aging, 1995-1996; nam_apap111-4.2_73 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - NYS Senate Legislative Bills on Aging, 1997; nam_apap111-4.2_74 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - NYS Welfare Reform, 1995-1996; nam_apap111-4.2_75 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - NYS Welfare, Regulatory Reform, 1995; nam_apap111-4.2_76 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - NYSSAC (New York StateWide Senior Action Council) Coalition vs. Executive Order # 20, Lawsuit, 1996; nam_apap111-4.2_77 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - NYSSAC Convention, 1993; nam_apap111-4.2_78 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - NYSSAC Convention Materials, 1995; nam_apap111-4.2_79 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - NYSSAC Convention Materials, 1996; nam_apap111-4.2_80 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - NYSSAC Convention Materials, 1996-1997; nam_apap111-4.2_81 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - NYSSAC Legislative Strategies and Priorities, 1973-1982; nam_apap111-4.2_82 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Older Americans Act, 1977-1982; nam_apap111-4.2_83 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Petitions Against Senate Bill S.1100, Undated; nam_apap111-4.2_84 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Regional Media Contacts, Undated; nam_apap111-4.2_85 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Rent Control, 1997; nam_apap111-4.2_86 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Retired Senior Volunteer Program (RSVP), 1986; nam_apap111-4.2_87 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Reverse Mortgage Legislation, 1994; nam_apap111-4.2_88 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Robin Hood Coalition for Fair State Taxes, 1992; nam_apap111-4.2_89 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Securities Private Enforcement Reform Act, H.R. 417 and Private Securities Litigation Reform Act, S.1976, 1994; nam_apap111-4.2_90 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Senior Citizen's Handbook, 1988; nam_apap111-4.2_91 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Senior Companion Project, 1992; nam_apap111-4.2_92 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Senior Companion Project, 1993; nam_apap111-4.2_93 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Senior Service Luncheon, 1993; nam_apap111-4.2_94 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Seniors for Adequate Social Security Newsletter, 1977-1984; nam_apap111-4.2_95 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - SENSES (Statewide Emergency Network for Social and Economic Security) Board of Directors' Meetings, 1991-1993; nam_apap111-4.2_96 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - SENSES Board of Directors' Meetings, 1994-1995; nam_apap111-4.2_97 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - SENSES Board of Directors' Retreat, 1993; nam_apap111-4.2_98 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - SENSES Personnel Committee, 1992; nam_apap111-4.2_99 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - SENSES Proposals for Counter Budget, 1993-1994; nam_apap111-4.2_100 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Social Security "Notch", Undated; nam_apap111-4.2_101 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - SSI (Supplemental Security Income) Action Letters, 1992; nam_apap111-4.2_102 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - SSI Advocacy Group, 1988-1991; nam_apap111-4.2_103 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - SSI Background, 1988-1989; nam_apap111-4.2_104 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - SSI Conference, 1989; nam_apap111-4.2_105 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - SSI Materials, 1985; 1988; nam_apap111-4.2_106 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - SSI Outreach Program, Proposal, 1988-1989; nam_apap111-4.2_107 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - SSI Outreach Program, 1991; nam_apap111-4.2_108 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - SSI Position Paper, 1990; nam_apap111-4.2_109 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - State Budget File, 1992; nam_apap111-4.2_110 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - State Communities Aid Association, 1991; nam_apap111-4.2_111 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - State Constitutional Convention Proposal, 1996; nam_apap111-4.2_112 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - State Programs for the Aging, 1989; nam_apap111-4.2_113 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - StateWide Platform, 1996; nam_apap111-4.2_114 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Statewide Youth Advocacy (SYA), 1991-1995; nam_apap111-4.2_115 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Student Association of the State University (SASU) response to the Governor's Budget, 1995; nam_apap111-4.2_116 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Tax Cut Opposition, 1995; nam_apap111-4.2_117 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Testimony Before Subcommittee on Aging, by Bonnie Ray, 1986; nam_apap111-4.2_118 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Testimony on Banking Bill by Greg Olsen, Public Hearing, 1994; nam_apap111-4.2_119 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - TRIAD-Police Relations, Orange County, NY case, 1995-1996; nam_apap111-4.2_120 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - TRIAD Program, Anti-Crime Bill S-4540-A / A-6706-A, 1993-1995; nam_apap111-4.2_121 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - University at Buffalo, State University of New York, Research Agreement, 1989; nam_apap111-4.2_122 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - University at Buffalo, State University of New York, Research Project, 1989; nam_apap111-4.2_123 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Violent Crime Initiative, 1995; nam_apap111-4.2_124 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Women's Issues, 1993; nam_apap111-4.2_125 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Consumer Fraud, 1988-1994; nam_apap111-4.3; 0.25 cubic ft.